Conservative Party Archive: Constituency Correspondence CPA CCO 1
Conservative Party Archive
- Constituency files, Sep 1953-Feb 1955
  - Area M - Wales and Monmouthshire, Sep 1953-Feb 1955
    - Denbigh, Wrexham, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/515/1; 1.0 file
    - Denbigh, Wrexham, By-Election (file A), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/515/2; 1.0 file
    - Denbigh, Wrexham, By-Election (file B), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/515/3; 1.0 file
    - Flint East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/516; 1.0 file
    - Flint West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/517; 1.0 file
    - Aberdare, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/518/1; 1.0 file
    - Aberdare, By-Election (file A), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/518/2; 1.0 file
    - Aberdare, By-Election (file B), Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/518/3; 1.0 file
    - Aberdare, By-Election - Organisation Department file, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/518/4; 1.0 file
    - Cardiff North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/519; 1.0 file
    - Cardiff South East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/520; 1.0 file
    - Cardiff West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/521; 1.0 file
    - Merthyr Tydfil, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/522; 1.0 file
    - Rhondda East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/523; 1.0 file
    - Rhondda West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/524; 1.0 file
    - Swansea East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/525; 1.0 file
    - Swansea West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/526; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Aberavon, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/527; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Barry, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/528; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Caerphilly, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/529; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Gower, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/530; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Neath, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/531; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Ogmore, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/532; 1.0 file
    - Glamorgan, Pontypridd, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/533; 1.0 file
    - Merioneth, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/534; 1.0 file
    - Newport, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/535; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Abertillery, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/536; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Bedwellty, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/537; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Ebbw Vale, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/538; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Monmouth, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/539; 1.0 file
    - Monmouthshire, Pontypool, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/540; 1.0 file
    - Montgomery, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/541; 1.0 file
    - Pembroke, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/542; 1.0 file
  - Area N - Scotland, Sep 1953-Feb 1955
    CCO 1/10/543-CCO 1/10/614
    - Aberdeen North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/543; 1.0 file
    - Aberdeen South, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/544; 1.0 file
    - Aberdeenshire East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/545; 1.0 file
    - Aberdeenshire West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/546; 1.0 file
    - Angus and Kincardineshire - Dundee, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/547/548; 1.0 file
    - Angus and Kincardineshire - Dundee East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/547; 1.0 file
    - Angus and Kincardineshire - Dundee West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/548; 1.0 file
    - Angus and Kincardineshire - North Angus and Mearns, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/549; 1.0 file
    - Angus and Kincardineshire - Angus South, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/550; 1.0 file
    - Argyll, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/551; 1.0 file
    - Ayr and Bute, Ayr, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/552; 1.0 file
    - Ayr and Bute, Bute and North Ayrshire, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/553; 1.0 file
    - Ayr and Bute, Central Ayrshire, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/554; 1.0 file
    - Ayr and Bute, Kilmarnock, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/555; 1.0 file
    - Ayr and Bute, South Ayrshire, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/556; 1.0 file
    - Banffshire, Banff, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/557; 1.0 file
    - Berwick and East Lothian, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/558; 1.0 file
    - Caithness and Sutherland, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/559; 1.0 file
    - Dumfries, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/560; 1.0 file
    - Dumbartonshire East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/561; 1.0 file
    - Dumbartonshire West, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/562; 1.0 file
    - Fife, Dunfermline Burgs, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/563; 1.0 file
    - Fife, Kirkaldy Burghs, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/564; 1.0 file
    - Fife, East Fife, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/565; 1.0 file
    - Fife, West Fife, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/566; 1.0 file
    - Inverness and Ross and Cromarty, Inverness, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/567/1; 1.0 file
    - Inverness and Ross and Cromarty, Inverness By-Election, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/567/2; 1.0 file
    - Inverness and Ross and Cromarty, Ross and Cromarty, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/568; 1.0 file
    - Inverness and Ross and Cromarty, Western Isles, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/569; 1.0 file
    - [Kircudbrighshire and Wigtownshire, Galloway], Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/570
    - Glasgow, Bridgeton, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/571; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Camlachie, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/572; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Cathcart, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/573; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Central, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/574; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Gorbels, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/575; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Govan, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/576; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Hillhead, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/577; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Kelvingrove, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/578; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Maryhill, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/579; 1.0 file
    - [Glasgow, Pollock], Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/580
    - Glasgow, Scotstoun, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/581; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Shettleston, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/582; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Springburn, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/583; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Tradeston, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/584; 1.0 file
    - Glasgow, Woodside, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/585; 1.0 file
    - Coatbridge and Airdrie, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/586; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Bothwell, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/587; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Hamilton, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/588; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Lanark, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/589; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Motherwell, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/590/1; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Motherwell By-Election, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/590/2; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, North, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/591; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Rutherglen, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/592; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh Central, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/593; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh East, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/594/1; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh East By-Election, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/594/2; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh Leith, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/595; 1.0 file
    - [Edinburgh North], Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/596/1
    - Edinburgh North By-Election, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/596/2; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh Pentlands, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/597; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh South, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/598; 1.0 file
    - [Edinburgh West], Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/599
    - Midlothian and Peebles, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/600; 1.0 file
    - Moray and Nairnshire, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/601; 1.0 file
    - Orkney and Zetland, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/602; 1.0 file
    - Perthshire and Kinross-shire, Kinross and West Perthshire, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/603; 1.0 file
    - Perthshire and Kinross-shire, Perth and East Perthshire, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/604; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire and Greenock, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/605; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire, Paisley, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/606; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire, East Renfrewshire, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/607; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire, West Renfrewshire, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/608; 1.0 file
    - Roxburgh and Selkirk, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/609; 1.0 file
    - Stirling and Falkirk Burghs, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/610; 1.0 file
    - Stirlingshire and Clackmannan, Clackmannan and East Stirlingshire, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/611; 1.0 file
    - Stirlingshire and Clackmannan, West Stirlingshire, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/612; 1.0 file
    - West Lothian, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/613; 1.0 file
    - [Vacant], Sep 1953-Feb 1955; [CCO 1/10/614]
  - Area O - Northern Ireland, Sep 1953-Feb 1955
    CCO 1/10/615-25
    - Northern Ireland, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/615/625; 1.0 file
    - Armagh By-Election, Sep 1953-Feb 1955; CCO 1/10/615; 1.0 file
- Constituency files, Mar 1955-Feb 1957
  - Area A - London, Mar 1955-Feb 1957
    CCO 1/11/1-CCO 1/11/42
    - Baron's Court, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/1; 1.0 file
    - Battersea North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/2; 1.0 file
    - Battersea South, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/3; 1.0 file
    - Bermondsey, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/4; 1.0 file
    - Bethnal Green, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/5; 1.0 file
    - Camberwell, Dulwich, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/6; 1.0 file
    - Camberwell, Peckham, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/7; 1.0 file
    - Chelsea, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/8; 1.0 file
    - Cities of London and Westminster, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/9/1; 1.0 file
    - City of London, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/9/2; 1.0 file
    - Abbey, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/9/3; 1.0 file
    - St. George's, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/9/4; 1.0 file
    - Deptford, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/10; 1.0 file
    - Fulham, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/11; 1.0 file
    - Greenwich, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/12; 1.0 file
    - Hackney Central, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/13; 1.0 file
    - Hammersmith North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/14; 1.0 file
    - Hampstead, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/15; 1.0 file
    - Holborn and St. Pancras South, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/16; 1.0 file
    - Islington East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/17; 1.0 file
    - Islington North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/18; 1.0 file
    - Islington South West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/19; 1.0 file
    - Kensington North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/20; 1.0 file
    - Kensington South, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/21; 1.0 file
    - Brixton (Lambeth), Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/22; 1.0 file
    - Norwood (Lambeth), Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/23; 1.0 file
    - Vauxhall (Lambeth), Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/24; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/25; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham South, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/26; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/27; 1.0 file
    - Paddington North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/28; 1.0 file
    - Paddington South, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/29; 1.0 file
    - Poplar, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/30; 1.0 file
    - St. Marylebone, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/31; 1.0 file
    - St. Pancras North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/32; 1.0 file
    - Shoreditch and Finsbury, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/33; 1.0 file
    - Southwark, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/34; 1.0 file
    - Stepney, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/35; 1.0 file
    - Stoke Newington and Hackney North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/36; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth Central, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/37; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth Clapham, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/38; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth Putney, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/39; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth Streatham, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/40; 1.0 file
    - Woolwich East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/41; 1.0 file
    - Woolwich West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/42/1; 1.0 file
    - University of London Graduates Association, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/42/2; 1.0 file
  - Area B - Northern, Mar 1955-Feb 1957
    CCO 1/11/43-CCO 1/11/76
    - Carlisle, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/43; 1.0 file
    - Cumbria, Penrith and the Border Division, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/44; 1.0 file
    - Cumbria, Whitehaven, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/45; 1.0 file
    - Cumbria, Workington, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/46; 1.0 file
    - Darlington, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/47; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/48/49; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead, East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/48; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead, West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/49/1; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead, West, By-Election (file A), Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/49/2; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead, West, By-Election - Organisation Department file, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/49/3; 1.0 file
    - Jarrow, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/50; 1.0 file
    - South Shields, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/51; 1.0 file
    - Stockton-on-Tees, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/52; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/53/54; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/53; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland South, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/54; 1.0 file
    - The Hartlepools, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/55; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Bishop Auckland, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/56; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Blaydon, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/57/1; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Blaydon, By-Election (file A), Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/57/2; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Blaydon, By-Election - Organisation Department file, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/57/3; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Chester-le-Street, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/58/1; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Chester-le-Street, By-Election (file A), Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/58/2; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Chester-le-Street, By-Election - Organisation Department file, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/58/3; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Consett, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/59; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Durham, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/60; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Easington, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/61; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Houghton-le-Spring, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/62; 1.0 file
    - Durham, North West Durham, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/63; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Sedgefield, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/64; 1.0 file
    - Blyth, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/65; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle Central, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/66; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/67; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/68; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/69; 1.0 file
    - Tynemouth, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/70; 1.0 file
    - Wallsend, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/71; 1.0 file
    - Berwick on Tweed, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/72; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle, Hexham, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/73; 1.0 file
    - Northumberland, Morpeth, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/74; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/75/76; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/75; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/76; 1.0 file
  - Area C - North West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957
    CCO 1/11/77-CCO 1/11/155
    - Altrincham and Sale, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/77; 1.0 file
    - Bebington, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/78; 1.0 file
    - Birkenhead, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/79; 1.0 file
    - Stockport, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/80/81; 1.0 file
    - Stockport North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/80; 1.0 file
    - Stockport South, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/81; 1.0 file
    - Wallasey, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/82; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Cheadle, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/83; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, City of Chester, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/84/1; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, City of Chester, By-Election (file A), Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/84/2; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, City of Chester, By-Election - Organisation Department file, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/84/3; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Crewe, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/85; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Knutsford, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/86; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Macclesfield, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/87; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Nantwich, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/88; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Northwich, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/89; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Runcorn, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/90; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Stalybridge and Hyde, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/91; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Wirral, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/92; 1.0 file
    - Accrington, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/93; 1.0 file
    - Ashton-under-Lyne, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/94; 1.0 file
    - Barrow-in-Furness, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/95; 1.0 file
    - Blackburn, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/96; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/97/98; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/97; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool South, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/98; 1.0 file
    - Bolton, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/99/100; 1.0 file
    - Bolton East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/99; 1.0 file
    - Bolton West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/100; 1.0 file
    - Bootle, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/101; 1.0 file
    - Burnley, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/102; 1.0 file
    - Bury and Radcliffe, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/103; 1.0 file
    - Crosby, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/104; 1.0 file
    - Eccles, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/105; 1.0 file
    - Droylsden, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/106/1; 1.0 file
    - Central Lancashire Union, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/106/2; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/107/115; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Edgehill, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/107; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Exchange, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/108; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Garston, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/109; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Kirkdale, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/110; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Scotland, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/111; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Toxteth, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/112; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Walton, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/113; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Wavertree, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/114; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, West Derby, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/115; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/116/124; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Ardwick, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/116; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Blackley, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/117; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Cheetham, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/118; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Exchange, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/119; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Gorton, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/120; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Moss Side, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/121; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Openshaw, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/122; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Withington, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/123; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Wythenshawe, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/124; 1.0 file
    - Nelson and Colne, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/125; 1.0 file
    - Oldham, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/126/127; 1.0 file
    - Oldham East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/126; 1.0 file
    - Oldham West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/127; 1.0 file
    - Preston, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/128/129; 1.0 file
    - Preston North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/128; 1.0 file
    - Preston South, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/129; 1.0 file
    - Rochdale, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/130; 1.0 file
    - Rossendale, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/131; 1.0 file
    - St. Helen's, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/132; 1.0 file
    - Salford, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/133/134; 1.0 file
    - Salford East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/133; 1.0 file
    - Salford West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/134; 1.0 file
    - Southport, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/135; 1.0 file
    - Stretford, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/136; 1.0 file
    - Warrington, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/137; 1.0 file
    - Wigan, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/138; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Chorley, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/139; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Clithero, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/140; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Darwen, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/141; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Farnworth, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/142; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Heywood and Royton, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/143; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Huyton, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/144; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Ince, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/145; 1.0 file
    - [Lancashire, Lancaster], Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/146
    - Lancashire, Middleton and Prestwich, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/147; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Morecombe and Lonsdale, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/148; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Newton, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/149; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, North Fylde, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/150; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Ormskirk, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/151; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, South Fylde, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/152; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Westhoughton, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/153; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Widnes, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/154; 1.0 file
    - Westmorland, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/155; 1.0 file
  - Area D - Yorkshire, Mar 1955-Feb 1957
    CCO 1/11/156-CCO 1/11/209
    - Barnsley, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/156/1; 1.0 file
    - Mid Yorkshire Federation, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/156/2; 1.0 file
    - Batley and Morely, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/157; 1.0 file
    - Bradford, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/158/161; 1.0 file
    - Bradford East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/158; 1.0 file
    - Bradford North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/159; 1.0 file
    - Bradford South, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/160; 1.0 file
    - Bradford West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/161; 1.0 file
    - Brighouse and Spenborough, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/162; 1.0 file
    - Dewsbury, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/163; 1.0 file
    - Doncaster, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/164; 1.0 file
    - Halifax, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/165; 1.0 file
    - Huddersfield, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/166/167; 1.0 file
    - Huddersfield East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/166; 1.0 file
    - Huddersfield West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/167; 1.0 file
    - Keighley, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/168; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-Upon-Hull, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/169/171; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-Upon-Hull East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/169; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-Upon-Hull North, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/170; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-Upon-Hull West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/171; 1.0 file
    - Leeds, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/172/177; 1.0 file
    - Leeds East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/172; 1.0 file
    - Leeds North East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/173/1; 1.0 file
    - Leeds North East, By-Election (file A), Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/173/2; 1.0 file
    - Leeds North East, By-Election - Organisation Department file, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/173/3; 1.0 file
    - Leeds North West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/174; 1.0 file
    - Leeds South, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/175; 1.0 file
    - Leeds South East, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/176; 1.0 file
    - Leeds West, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/177; 1.0 file
    - Pontefract, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/178; 1.0 file
    - Pudsey, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/179; 1.0 file
    - Rotherham, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/180; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/181/186; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Attercliffe, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/181; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Brightside, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/182; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Hallam, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/183; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Healey, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/184; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Hillsborough, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/185; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Park, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/186; 1.0 file
    - Wakefield, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/187; 1.0 file
    - York, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/188; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Barkston Ash, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/189; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Bridlington, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/190; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Cleveland, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/191; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Colne Valley, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/192; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Dearne Valley, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/193; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Don Valley, Mar 1955-Feb 1957; CCO 1/11/194; 1.0 file